Let me do my job!
دعني اقوم بعملي!
I'm the nurse manager now,
أنا مدير التمريض الآن،
and I'm removing Samuel from under your monitoring.
وأنا أزيل صموئيل من تحت مراقبتك.
- But-- - But what, Olivia?
- لكن-- - لكن ماذا، أوليفيا؟
Mia's part of my family now, Ma.
أصبحت ميا جزءًا من عائلتي الآن، يا أمي.
She and Matmat are the most important to me right now.
إنها ومتمات هما الأهم بالنسبة لي الآن.
Once I prove that Ma'am Ingrid is still alive,
بمجرد أن أثبت أن السيدة إنغريد لا تزال على قيد الحياة،
I want her to pay for what she did to you.
أريدها أن تدفع ثمن ما فعلته بك.
But if I go down that path,
ولكن إذا ذهبت في هذا الطريق،
- Happy Day! - it might affect Mia.
- يوم سعيد! - قد يؤثر على ميا.
Am I one of those people you'll protect?
هل أنا واحد من هؤلاء الأشخاص الذين ستحميهم؟
Mia, you're part of our family now.
ميا، أنت جزء من عائلتنا الآن.
It's okay for Mia and Patpat to kiss
لا بأس أن يتبادل ميا وباتبات القبلات
as long as Mia and Patpat don't fight.
طالما أن ميا وباتبات لا يتقاتلان.
We're not leaving Mia.
نحن لا نترك ميا.
We'll stick together.
سوف نبقى معاً.
Matmat, I see you're painting again.
مطمات، أرى أنك ترسم مرة أخرى.
Mister Tommy!
السيد تومي!
H-Happy Day!
يوم سعيد!
I'm sure this will make you happy.
أنا متأكد من أن هذا سوف يجعلك سعيدًا.
- Here.
- هنا.
Thank you for all your help,
شكرًا لك على كل مساعدتك،
and for lending me that book.
ولإقراضي هذا الكتاب.
D-Did Mister Tommy love the book?
د- هل أحب السيد تومي الكتاب؟
Did he enjoy the story of "The Kid Batibat Visited"?
هل استمتعت بقصة "الطفل الذي زاره باتيبات"؟
Absolutely!
بالتأكيد!
- I know it by heart now.
- أنا أعرف ذلك عن ظهر قلب الآن.
By the way, Matmat…
بالمناسبة، مطمت...
are you able to paint butterflies now?
هل تستطيع رسم الفراشات الآن؟
Not yet.
ليس بعد.
Not yet, Mister Tommy.
ليس بعد، سيد تومي.
Matmat still can't paint butterflies.
لا يزال ماتمات غير قادر على رسم الفراشات.
But Matmat will try.
ولكن مطمات سوف يحاول.
He will keep trying.
سوف يستمر في المحاولة.
I'm curious.
أنا فضولي.
Who do you think will be the first between us?
من تعتقد أنه سيكون الأول بيننا؟
First in what, Mister Tommy?
أولاً في ماذا، سيد تومي؟
Is there a race?
هل هناك سباق؟
I'm not talking about a race.
أنا لا أتحدث عن سباق.
Who will be-- Who will be first?
من سيكون-- من سيكون الأول؟
You painting butterflies…
أنت ترسم الفراشات...
…or me getting past my trauma?
...أو هل أستطيع تجاوز صدمتي؟
It… It depends on who will find the door first.
هذا...يعتمد على من سيجد الباب أولاً.
Mister Tommy or Matmat?
السيد تومي أو ماتمات؟
You remember!
هل تتذكر؟
You're right!
أنت على حق!
May we find the door at the same time,
نتمنى أن نجد الباب في نفس الوقت،
so we can leave together.
لذا يمكننا المغادرة معًا.
W-We will leave side by side.
س-سنغادر جنبًا إلى جنب.
- Ma'am Eden. - Patrick.
- سيدتي إيدن. - باتريك.
I was hoping to talk to you.
كنت أتمنى التحدث معك.
What about?
ماذا عن؟
I want you to give Mia a heads-up,
أريدك أن تخبر ميا بذلك،
since you're always together.
لأنكم دائما معًا.
Mia is aware that--
ميا تدرك أن--
Let me finish.
دعني أنهي.
All I'm saying is,
كل ما أقوله هو،
if she needs to organize any documents
إذا كانت بحاجة إلى تنظيم أي مستندات
or say anything to her father,
أو تقول أي شيء لأبيها،
now is the time.
الآن هو الوقت.
Alright, I'll tell her that.
حسنًا، سأخبرها بذلك.
Make sure she understands, Patrick.
تأكد من أنها تفهم، باتريك.
So that on her next visit,
حتى في زيارتها القادمة،
she can focus on her father.
يمكنها التركيز على والدها.
Nurse…
ممرضة…
Nurse?
ممرضة؟
Are you a nurse?
هل أنت ممرضة؟
Samuel.
صموئيل.
It's me.
هذا أنا.
Get me out of here.
أخرجني من هنا.
Please get me out of this place.
من فضلك أخرجني من هذا المكان.
I've had enough of this place.
لقد سئمت من هذا المكان.
I don't want to die here.
لا أريد أن أموت هنا.
Mia.
لي.
Matmat. You're here.
مطمت.أنت هنا.
How long have you been here?
منذ متى وأنت هنا؟
Mmm. Matmat just finished his work at OK Hospital.
ممم. انتهى ماتمات للتو من عمله في مستشفى أوك.
Perfect.
ممتاز.
I have something to discuss with you.
عندي شيء أريد مناقشته معك.
Is this the latest draft of your illustrations?
هل هذه هي المسودة الأخيرة من رسوماتك التوضيحية؟
T-Those are Mister Box,
T-هؤلاء هم السيد بوكس،
Mask Boy,
فتى القناع
and Princess Without Feelings.
والأميرة بلا مشاعر.
They don't have faces.
ليس لديهم وجوه.
They're human characters. They need faces.
إنهم شخصيات بشرية، يحتاجون إلى وجوه.
Mask Boy and Mister Box…
فتى القناع وسيد الصندوق…
T-They have their faces hidden.
ت-لقد اخفوا وجوههم.
They don't need f-facial details.
لا يحتاجون إلى تفاصيل الوجه.
In all of my books,
في جميع كتبي،
the characters have faces.
الشخصيات لها وجوه.
They may not have proper nouns as names,
قد لا يكون لديهم أسماء خاصة،
but it's important that they do have faces.
ولكن من المهم أن يكون لديهم وجوه.
It's hard. It's hard.
إنه صعب.إنه صعب.
M-Matmat just cannot draw faces.
لا يستطيع M-Matmat رسم الوجوه.
It's too hard. Too hard.
إنه صعب جدًا. صعب جدًا.
Listen, Matmat.
إستمع يا مطمت.
You have a poster of expressions, right?
لديك ملصق تعبيرات، أليس كذلك؟
You can learn from it.
يمكنك التعلم منه.
Matmat looks at it.
مطمت ينظر إليه.
How about you start practicing?
ماذا عن أن تبدأ في التدريب؟
You want Matmat to practice?
هل تريد ماتمات للتدرب؟
Yes.
نعم.
They say practice makes progress.
يقولون أن الممارسة تؤدي إلى التقدم.
Start by drawing expressions.
ابدأ برسم التعابير.
As you go, imagine what the characters look like.
أثناء تقدمك، تخيل كيف تبدو الشخصيات.
Once you can do that, you'll be able to draw their faces.
بمجرد أن تتمكن من القيام بذلك، سوف تكون قادرًا على رسم وجوههم.
Mmm.
ممم.
Matmat.
شكرًا لك.
I know you can do it.
أعلم أنك قادر على فعل ذلك.
You're talented, observant…
أنت موهوب، ومراقب.
But we have a deadline to work to.
ولكن لدينا موعد نهائي للعمل عليه.
You must finish everything by next week.
يجب عليك الانتهاء من كل شيء بحلول الأسبوع المقبل.
Next week? M-Mister Box and friends need to have faces?
الأسبوع القادم؟ هل يحتاج السيد بوكس ​​وأصدقاؤه إلى وجوه؟
Yes. You need to turn in the final draft.
نعم. عليك تسليم المسودة النهائية.
N-Next week.
ن-الاسبوع القادم.
Deadline.
موعد التسليم.
Faces.
وجوه.
Matmat can't draw them.
مطمت لا يستطيع رسمهم.
Mister Samuel.
السيدة صموئيل.
You're the only one who can tell me the truth.
أنت الوحيد الذي يستطيع أن يقول لي الحقيقة.
Is your wife still alive?
هل زوجتك لا تزال على قيد الحياة؟
Sir Samuel…
السير صموئيل…
This is for your daughter's sake.
هذا من أجل ابنتك.
Is Ma'am Ingrid here in this hospital?
هل السيدة إنغريد هنا في هذا المستشفى؟
Ingrid…?
إنغريد...؟
My wife?
زوجتي؟
Yes.
نعم.
She's dead.
لقد ماتت.
My wife is dead.
لقد ماتت زوجتي.
She can't…
إنها لا تستطيع...
She can't. She can't.
لا تستطيع. لا تستطيع.
She can't come back.
لا يمكنها العودة.
She's dead--
لقد ماتت--
Sir Samuel! Sir Samuel!
سيدي صموئيل! سيدي صموئيل!
- What did you do? - He suddenly…
- ماذا فعلت؟ - فجأة...
Come on.
تعال.
Samuel!
صموئيل!
Samuel, can you hear me?
صموئيل هل تستطيع أن تسمعني؟
You're in the hospital.
أنت في المستشفى.
I can take care of him, Olivia.
أستطيع الاعتناء به، أوليفيا.
Patrick!
باتريك!
How are you?
كيف حالك؟
I haven't seen you.
لم أرك.
I'm good.
أنا بخير.
About the thing you were asking me the other day.
بخصوص الشيء الذي سألتني عنه في اليوم الآخر.
With Ma'am Ingrid and your mom.
مع السيدة إنغريد ووالدتك.
Is it okay now?
هل الأمر بخير الآن؟
Why do you ask?
لماذا تسأل؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
It's just that you looked worried.
إن الأمر فقط هو أنك تبدو قلقًا.
Don't worry. It's all good.
لا تقلق، كل شيء على ما يرام.
Will those three find what they're looking for?
هل سيجد هؤلاء الثلاثة ما يبحثون عنه؟
Hey!
يا!
No reading.
لا قراءة.
Neither of you won't even share it with me.
لن يشارك أي منكما هذا معي حتى.
No.
لا.
You have to wait until it's done.
يتوجب عليك الانتظار حتى يتم الانتهاء منه.
That’s too much of a suspense.
هذا الكثير من التشويق.
Stay outside. I'm still writing.
ابقى بالخارج. مازلت أكتب.
Go.
يذهب.
You don't want to go? Do you have anything to say?
لا تريد الذهاب؟ هل لديك شيء لتقوله؟
What is it?
ما هذا؟
It's about,
إنه يتعلق بـ
Sir Samuel.
السير صموئيل.
He's in the isolation room again.
لقد عاد إلى غرفة العزل مرة أخرى.
His condition worsens, Mia.
حالته تزداد سوءًا، ميا.
And so?
و ماذا إذن؟
Mia…
لي…
Death can't undo what he did to me.
الموت لا يستطيع التراجع عما فعله بي.
- Mia-- - Go.
- لي-- - اذهب.
I don't want you to have regrets.
لا أريدك أن تشعر بالندم.
I said go, Patrick.
قلت اذهب يا باتريك.
Why are you still alive?!
لماذا أنت على قيد الحياة حتى الآن؟
You should be dead!
يجب أن تكون ميتا!
Sir Samuel! Sir Samuel, stop it!
سيدي صموئيل! سيدي صموئيل، توقف!
You are your mother's daughter.
أنت ابنة أمك.
Her blood is your blood.
دمها هو دمك.
Her character is your character.
شخصيتها هي شخصيتك.
You can't run away from her.
لا يمكنك الهروب منها .
He's in the isolation room again.
لقد عاد إلى غرفة العزل مرة أخرى.
His condition worsens, Mia.
حالته تزداد سوءًا، ميا.
I don't want you to have regrets.
لا أريدك أن تشعر بالندم.
Oh, Vincent.
أوه، فينسنت.
For you.
لك.
Apologies. My friend just returned from the farm in Benguet.
عذراً. صديقي عاد للتو من المزرعة في بنجويت.
That's why it took me a while.
لهذا السبب استغرق الأمر مني بعض الوقت.
You shouldn't have bothered.
لا ينبغي أن تهتم.
You always tell me not to bother.
أنت دائما تقول لي لا أزعج نفسي.
But, I want to.
ولكنني أريد ذلك.
I like doing things for you.
أحب أن أفعل الأشياء من أجلك.
I'm sorry I didn't message you while I was in Manila.
أنا آسف لأنني لم أرسل لك رسالة أثناء وجودي في مانيلا.
This is all Madeth's fault.
كل هذا خطأ ماديث.
Madeth?
ماديث؟
- Yeah. - What did she do?
- نعم. - ماذا فعلت؟
I should not have listened to her gut feeling.
لا ينبغي لي أن أستمع إلى حدسها.
I should, listen to you alone.
ينبغي لي أن أستمع إليك وحدك.
Looks like you've contemplated a lot while you were in Manila.
يبدو أنك فكرت كثيرًا أثناء وجودك في مانيلا.
All I did there was work.
كل ما فعلته هناك هو العمل.
And my business dinner with Erica--
وعشاء العمل مع إيريكا--
We didn't even follow up on.
ولم نتابع الأمر حتى.
And to be honest,
ولكي أكون صادقا،
I'm able to think more sensibly here in Maravida.
أنا قادر على التفكير بشكل أكثر منطقية هنا في مارافيدا.
Hmm.
همم.
I realized that, I shouldn't be rushing into things.
لقد أدركت أنني لا ينبغي أن أتسرع في الأمور.
Patience is the key.
الصبر هو المفتاح .
Especially when it comes to the things
وخاصة عندما يتعلق الأمر بالأشياء
I like.
انا احب.
- I'll try this one. - Yeah!
- سأجرب هذا. - نعم!
- My mom might like coffee. - Sure!
- ربما تحب أمي القهوة. - بالتأكيد!
Patrick.
باتريك.
Ma'am Eden.
السيدة عدن.
Why did you lie?
لماذا كذبت؟
What?
ماذا؟
You said, you didn't do anything to Samuel.
لقد قلت أنك لم تفعل أي شيء لصموئيل.
But I saw on the CCTV footage that you were talking to him.
لكنني رأيت في لقطات كاميرا المراقبة أنك كنت تتحدث معه.
Ma'am--
سيدتي--
Do you want me to report this to Dr. Anok?
هل تريد مني أن أبلغ الدكتور أنوك بهذا الأمر؟
You've committed countless offenses, Patrick.
لقد ارتكبت عددًا لا يحصى من الجرائم، باتريك.
This is grounds for your termination.
هذا هو سبب إنهاء خدمتك.
Ma'am, I didn't want that to happen to Sir Samuel.
سيدتي، لم أكن أريد أن يحدث ذلك للسير صموئيل.
What did you say to him anyway?
ماذا قلت له على أية حال؟
For him to react that way?
أن يتفاعل بهذه الطريقة؟
I asked him how he was doing.
سألته كيف حاله؟
I mentioned Mia's name.
ذكرت اسم ميا.
Is it bad to mention his daughter's name?
هل من السيء ذكر اسم ابنته؟
You shouldn't be doing things that you're aren't ordered to do.
لا ينبغي عليك أن تفعل أشياء لم يؤمرك أحد بفعلها.
You didn't even know that you were ruining a patient's treatment.
لم تكن تعلم حتى أنك كنت تدمر علاج المريض.
Hmm.
همم.
Matmat can't draw your face.
ماتمات لا يستطيع رسم وجهك.
Is that your sad face?
هل هذا وجهك الحزين؟
Yes, Matmat. This is a sad face.
نعم يا مطمت، هذا وجه حزين.
Look at me. I was doing this.
انظروا إليّ، كنت أفعل هذا.
I'm sighing.
أنا أتنهد.
And my eyes were looking down. It was doing this.
وعيناي كانتا تنظران إلى الأسفل. كان يفعل هذا.
Right?
يمين؟
Sad. That's sadness.
حزين. هذا هو الحزن.
That's hard. Matmat is having a hard time.
هذا صعب. ماتمات يمر بوقت عصيب.
Alright, alright, Matmat.
حسنًا، حسنًا، مطمت.
I'll give you another example of sadness.
سأعطيك مثالا آخر للحزن.
Let me give you one more. Um…
دعني أعطيك واحدة أخرى.
Ahh…
آه…
Okay, there's that sadness.
حسنًا، هناك هذا الحزن.
This one is a different kind. Here, hold on.
هذا نوع مختلف. انتظر.
Time to be an actor.
حان الوقت لكي تصبح ممثلاً.
Huh, huh…
هاه هاه…
- Aww… - Ugly, ugly!
- أوووه... - قبيح، قبيح!
- That's now how to be sad. - Wait, wait, Matmat!
- هكذا تكون حزينًا الآن. - انتظر، انتظر، مطمت!
- It's a different kind! - Hard. So hard.
- إنه نوع مختلف! - صعب. صعب جدًا.
- No thanks, too hard! - Hold on, hold on, Matmat!
- لا، شكرًا، صعب جدًا! - انتظر، انتظر، ماتمات!
I have another kind of sadness. It's a very different one.
لديّ حزنٌ من نوعٍ آخر، حزنٌ مختلفٌ تمامًا.
Let's pretend that Gemma doesn't want to date me.
فلنتظاهر أن جيما لا تريد مواعدتي.
- I'd be sad if she said no. - Matmat? Matmat?
- سأحزن لو قالت لا. - مطمت؟ مطمت؟
Matmat, is that you? It is Matmat!
مطمت، هل هذا أنت؟ إنه مطمت!
I knew I heard you, Matmat.
لقد عرفت أنني سمعتك، ماتمات.
What's wrong Matmat? Are you guys fighting?
ما بك يا ماتمات؟ هل تتشاجران؟
No, Matmat asked me to help him with drawing expressions.
لا، لقد طلب مني مطمت أن أساعده في رسم التعابير.
He's practicing how to draw expressions.
إنه يتدرب على كيفية رسم التعابير.
Drawing expressions? Matmat, that means
رسم التعابير؟ ماتمات، هذا يعني
- you guys need a model, right? - Oh!
-أنتم بحاجة إلى نموذج، أليس كذلك؟ -أوه!
I'm very expressive, Matmat.
أنا معبر جدًا، مطمت.
- I can be your model, Matmat. - Oh, oh!
- يمكنني أن أكون نموذجك، ماتمات. - أوه، أوه!
- Look at me, Matmat! - Wow!
- انظر إليّ يا مطمت! - واو!
- Here's another pose, Matmat! - Oh, wow!
- وهنا وضعية أخرى، ماتمات! - أوه، واو!
- Let me be your model, Matmat. - Okay, okay.
- دعني أكون نموذجك، ماتمات. - حسنًا، حسنًا.
- M-Matmat will draw M-Madeth. - Me? Really?
- م-ماتمات سيرسم م-مادهيث. - أنا؟ حقًا؟
Mm-hmm, that's me, Matmat.
مممم، هذا أنا، ماتمات.
What do you need, Matmat?
ماذا تحتاج يا مطمت؟
Happy. I need happy, Madeth.
سعيدة. أنا بحاجة إلى السعادة، ماديث.
I can do that, Matmat!
أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك، ماتمات!
What kind of happy? How happy do you want, Matmat?
أي سعادة تريد يا مطمت؟
Happy like I just won the lottery?
سعيدة وكأنني فزت للتو باليانصيب؟
Or happy like you just need an ID picture?
أم أنك سعيد وكأنك تحتاج فقط إلى صورة هوية؟
One, two, three!
واحد اثنين ثلاثة!
- Ooh! - Like that, Matmat?
- أوه! - مثل ذلك، ماتمات؟
Or happy like my crush finally noticed me?
أم أنني سعيدة لأن حبيبي لاحظ وجودي أخيرا؟
- I don't want to. Too hard. - Oh.
- لا أريد ذلك. صعب جدًا. - أوه.
You don't want that, Matmat? Hold on, Madeth.
ألا تريد ذلك يا ماتمات؟ انتظر يا ماديث.
Didn't like hers? It was good!
لم يعجبك؟ كان جيدًا!
Like the one who won the lottery, draw that one!
مثل الذي فاز باليانصيب، ارسم ذلك!
Oh, oh no! Madeth, what was that?
أوه، أوه لا! ماديث، ماذا كان هذا؟
Why are you feeling this way.
لماذا تشعر بهذه الطريقة؟
Why would you say that? Noticed by your crush?
لماذا تقول ذلك؟ هل لاحظه من تحب؟
What did my crush notice? What is it, Madeth?
ماذا لاحظ حبيبي؟ ما الأمر يا ماديث؟
So, I'm the one you want to drink with?
إذن، أنا الشخص الذي تريد أن تشرب معه؟
Is this about your papa?
هل هذا يتعلق بوالدك؟
Gemma.
جيما.
What if we were switched at birth?
ماذا لو تم تبديلنا عند الولادة؟
What if Miss Li was my mama, and you had my papa?
ماذا لو كانت الآنسة لي أمي، وكان لديك أبي؟
- Mia… - What would happen?
- ميا... - ماذا سيحدث؟
Come on.
تعال.
It's just a "what if."
إنه مجرد "ماذا لو".
If it was like that, and you were mama's daughter…
لو كان الأمر كذلك، وكنتِ ابنة ماما...
She'd pinch your inner thigh for talking like that.
إنها سوف تضغط على فخذك الداخلي إذا تحدثت بهذه الطريقة.
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
As for you…
أما أنت…
My parents would be so happy having a nice daughter like you.
والداي سيكونان سعيدين جدًا لو أنجبا ابنة لطيفة مثلك.
Someone who would be afraid of them.
شخص ما سيكون خائفا منهم.
Afraid?
خائف؟
You're afraid of your papa?
هل أنت خائف من باباك؟
I'm afraid of my mama.
أنا خائفة من أمي.
That's why I tried to be a good daughter growing up.
لهذا السبب حاولت أن أكون ابنة جيدة عندما كبرت.
Because I was afraid of her.
لأني كنت خائفة منها.
Mama?
ماما؟
Mama, I'm hungry.
ماما أنا جائع.
Aren't we going to eat dinner?
ألا نذهب لتناول العشاء؟
You're disturbing me!
أنت تزعجني!
Didn't I tell you to not disturb me while I'm writing?
ألم أخبرك ألا تزعجني أثناء كتابتي؟
I just didn't want her to hate me.
لم أكن أريدها أن تكرهني.
I used to think she was the only one that liked me.
كنت أعتقد أنها الوحيدة التي تحبني.
Until I met him.
حتى التقيت به.
I wanted to go with him…
أردت أن أذهب معه...
so that I didn't need to live life in fear.
حتى لا أضطر إلى أن أعيش حياتي في خوف.
But those plans…
ولكن تلك الخطط...
were thwarted by her.
تم إحباطها من قبلها.
You're so luck to have a supportive mother like Miss Li.
أنت محظوظ جدًا لأن لديك أمًا داعمة مثل الآنسة لي.
As for my papa,
أما بالنسبة لأبي،
I'm not afraid of him.
أنا لا أخاف منه.
I just…
انا فقط…
never felt his presence. Never.
لم أشعر بوجوده أبدًا. أبدًا.
He was just there.
لقد كان هناك للتو.
He didn't do anything for you?
لم يفعل لك شيئا؟
Like what?
مثل ماذا؟
Try to protect me from the cruel ways of my mother?
حاول أن تحميني من أساليب أمي القاسية؟
He didn't do anything.
لم يفعل شيئا.
Wait…
انتظر…
There was one thing.
كان هناك شيئا واحدا.
He read me a fairytale.
لقد قرأ لي قصة خيالية.
That's it?
هذا كل شيء؟
Yeah, just once.
نعم مرة واحدة فقط.
Nothing more.
لا شيء أكثر.
Do you want a drink of water?
هل تريد شرب الماء؟
I want to…
أريد أن...
I want to tell the truth.
أريد أن أقول الحقيقة.
What's the truth?
ما هي الحقيقة؟
I did…
فعلتُ…
…something bad.
…شيئا سيئا.
Don't think too hard, Samuel.
لا تفكر كثيرا يا صموئيل.
I killed her.
لقد قتلتها.
I killed my wife.
لقد قتلت زوجتي.
You two are mine and mine alone.
أنتما الاثنين لي وحدي.
I killed her.
لقد قتلتها.
There are only two people in this hospital that could be Ingrid.
هناك شخصين فقط في هذا المستشفى يمكن أن يكونا إنغريد.
They're the two people who are connected to Mia's papa.
إنهم الشخصان المرتبطان بوالد ميا.
Mia saw how I killed my wife!
لقد رأت ميا كيف قتلت زوجتي!
Is that why you strangled Mia?
هل هذا هو السبب الذي جعلك تخنق ميا؟
No matter what I discover, I'll get you out, Mia.
مهما اكتشفت، سأخرجك، ميا.
Do you know where Mia is? Mister Samuel is missing.
هل تعرف أين ميا؟ السيد صموئيل مفقود.